surveilzone.com 2016-03-25

# Privacy Policy

| 

  At **[SurveilZone.com](http://www.surveilzone.com/)** , your privacy is very important to us, we take extensive measures to ensure that your shopping experience with us is safe and secure. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy.

**Information We Collect and How We Use It**

Order Processing:

  When you place an order with us, we will need to collect your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as your credit card number. Information collected is to process order and updates of order confirmation and shipment status. During the order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number, PayPal account email. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. We employ third party bank merchant who has limited access to your personal information to perform payment approvals. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. 

**Shipping & Delivery:**

  We employ third party shipping carriers to handle and send out the packages. Information they can access is recipient’s name, shipping address and phone number (necessary to expedited shipping), they will not use it for other purpose.

**Subscribers:**

  For newsletter subscriber, your contact information will be used for the delivery of newsletter, promotion & periodic special offers. 

**Cookies:**

  We use cookies on this site. Cookies are small files that are stored by your browser on your computer that may contain personal information about you, your computer, or your experience on a particular web site. It lets you shop our site, place items in your cart and return several days later without having to reenter the information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. Besides, cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

**Security:**

  We take every precaution to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information (such as credit card data or your account information), the Site may utilize the industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. SSL provides two way encryption for information sent between the visitor and the web site. You can verify this by looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. All of your personally & financially information is kept in a secured environment, and only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information.

**Contacting[SurveilZone.com](http://www.surveilzone.com/)**

  If you have any questions or concerns about privacy policy, please visit our Contact Us page or click on Live Chat on the lower right corner to get in touch with us.
